[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "Full from of RAM is ?",
"a": "Read All Memory",
"b": "Random Access Memory",
"c": "Read Access Machine",
"d": "Real Access Machine",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "What does WWW stand for ?",
"a": "World With Web",
"b": "Web Wide World",
"c": "World Wide Web",
"d": "Wide Web World",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "Google Chrome is a ?",
"a": "Text editor",
"b": "Browser",
"c": "Anitivirus",
"d": "Software to draw",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "Monitor is used to ?",
"a": "Type",
"b": "Print",
"c": "Display",
"d": "Scan",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "Computer runs on ?",
"a": "Air",
"b": "Electricity",
"c": "Water",
"d": "Petrol",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "Mouse is moved on a ?",
"a": "Table",
"b": "Screen",
"c": "Mouse Pad",
"d": "CPU",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "Software is a ?",
"a": "Physical part",
"b": "Hardware",
"c": "Program",
"d": "Wire",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "The full from of USB is ?",
"a": "Unique Serial Bus",
"b": "Universal Serial Bus",
"c": "Universal System Box",
"d": "United System Bus",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "A file is saved in a ?",
"a": "Printer",
"b": "Monitor",
"c": "Folder",
"d": "Mouse",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "Shortcut for copy is ?",
"a": "Ctrl + P",
"b": "Ctrl + C",
"c": "Ctcl + V",
"d": "Ctcl + X",
"correct": "b"
}
]